l don't think I wanna play a game.
(Penny:)They're playing one across the hall.
We should too.
(Penny:)Okay, we are gonna take turns
bouncing a quarter off the table.
(Penny:)If it goes into this cup,
the other person has to drink.
Then you get to go again, and you ki...
- Like that?
- Wow, yeah, beginner's luck.
(Penny:)So now I will drink this entire cup of beer...
(Penny:)...and you will go again and we can...
(Penny:)All right, so, yeah.
Okay, now I'm gonna drink this entire cup.
(Penny:)And then I'm going to drink another one.
(Penny:)Okay, seriously, stop. What the hell?
l spent my childhood throwing coins
into wishing wells hoping for friends.
(Amy:)At a certain point, you start doing
trick shots to keep things interesting.
Oh, give me a second
to catch up here, hold on.